# **Gracielle** Pestana

## **Product** Designer

I'm a designer based in Brazil with a passion for understanding users' behaviors and making solutions that better connect with them and their needs. My strengths are working based on data, analyzing, testing, and adapting visuals to the user's profile. I have over 10 years of working with Design, and 4 are focusing on UX & UI in games.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Senior Product Designer**

Gazeus Games | Present - April 2021

- Benchmark, research, prototyping, user testing, surveys, and data analysis;
- Wireframes, user interfacing, HUDs, UX animations;
- Responsibility to the UX/UI of Spades and Euchre Jogatina and now Buraco Jogatina;
- Importing Assets to Unity, animating in unity or in Spine;
- Responsible for the Art Department software inventory census that resulted in a 15% cost reduction:
- UX evangelist, introducing and validating with the Design/Product teams new tools to improve the workflow, prototyping, and testing;
- Training other designers Unity UI basics and best practices;
- · Create and maintain Design System;
- · Documentation of features.

+55 21 9 8177.0652

gracielle.pestana@gmail.com

www.graciellepestana.com

linkedin.com/graciellepestana

dribbble.com/grapestana

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Graphic Design**

Senac Rio | Dec. 2013

#### Web Design

Oi Kabum | 2009 - 2010

### **SKILLS**

Sketch | Figma | Spine |
Lookback | Playtest Cloud |
Proto.io | Invision | Zeplin |
Illustrator | Photoshop | After
Effects | Office | Unity | Git |
Firebase | Jira | Confluence

Creative | Organized | Like to learn new tools | Teamship |
Communicator

## **LANGUAGES**

#### **Portuguese**

Native

#### **English**

Proficient

#### **Spanish**

Advanced



#### **Product Designer**

Gazeus Games | April 2021 – August 2018



- Benchmark, research, prototyping, user testing, surveys, and data analysis;
- · Wireframes, user interfacing, HUDs, ux animations;
- Responsability to the UX/UI of Spades and Euchre Jogatina;
- · Importing Assets to Unity, animating in unity or in Spine;
- UX evangelist, introducing and validating with the Design/Product teams new tools to improve the workflow, prototyping, and testing;
- · Create and maintain Design System;
- Documentation of features.

#### **Marketing Designer**

Gazeus Games | July 2018 - February 2016

- · Creating campaigns for Monetization;
- · Creating social campaigns on social media;
- · Visuals for Stores, working with the ASO team.

#### **Technical Designer (Games)**

Tamboro Educacional | January 2016 – June 2014

- · Wireframes, user interfacing, assets;
- · Importing Assets to Flash, animating in Flash & Spritesheets;
- · Working with educational games.

#### **PREVIOUS EXPERIENCES**

#### **Graphic Designer**

14 Agência de Conteúdo Digital | May 2014 – July 2013

#### Intern

Studio Attila | June 2013 – April 2012

#### **Web Designer**

Tamboro Educional | March 2012 – June 2011

